# **Ashley Littlewood**

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

ashley.littlewood22@gmail.com 07955744574

www.ashtagging.com

#### Links

Personal Website

LinkedIn

**GitHub** 

#### Skills

React

JavaScript

C#

ASP.NET

CSS

Sass

HTML

**SQL** 

## **Hobbies & Interests**

An accomplished chess player, having played for the England junior team. Won numerous individual and team tournaments in addition to being the team captain on several occasions. Keen photographer and traveller, having travelled solo around 35 countries.

#### **Profile**

Junior software developer with a wide range of experience producing web applications using a variety of languages, technologies and platforms such as JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, SQL, NoSQL, C#, and .NET. I am currently searching for a new role to further develop my knowledge within a professional working environment. Please visit the links to view my personal website, GitHub and LinkedIn.

## **Education**

#### MSc Computing, Sheffield Hallam University, (Distinction)

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021

#### BSc Mathematics, University of Leeds, (Hons)

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2016

#### A-Levels, Thomas Rotherham College

SEPTEMBER 2010 - JULY 2013

- A-Levels: Further Maths (A) Maths (A) Economics (B) General Studies (B)
- AS levels: Physics (C) Biology (C)

#### GCSEs, Oakwood High School

SEPTEMBER 2005 - JULY 2010

• 10 GCSE's from (A\*-C) including (A\*) Maths, (A\*) Science, (A) English

#### **Courses**

#### The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp, Udemy

OCTOBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022

# Complete guide to ASP.NET Core MVC (.NET 5), Udemy

JANUARY 2021 - MARCH 2021

## Learn (JavaScript, C#, ASP.NET, SQL, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML), CodeCademy

DECEMBER 2020 - APRIL 2021

# **Employment History**

## **Customer Service Administrator, Sherwin Williams**

SEPTEMBER 2021 — PRESENT

- Consulted with external parties to resolve quantity discrepancies with effective and collaborative solutions
- Utilised Salesforce to manage user issues, respond to support tickets and monitor the request pipeline
- Processed orders, credits, debits and returns based upon customer requirements using ERP and CRM systems

#### **Production Planner, Sherwin Williams**

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

- Effectively planned batches on production lines whilst adhering to tight schedules and demand planning requirements
- Developed an improved system for planning batches, which significantly reduced the quantity of waste material.
- Analysed batch variance reports and investigated production batches with substantial cost variances

# Airport Services Administrator, Qantas, Sydney (Australia Working Holiday Visa)

DECEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

- Lead admin for an in-house business project, adhering to corporate NDA
  in a media-sensitive role by organising contingency training for head office
  employees in the event of unionised industrial action
- Fostered a high rate of colleague participation by designing a strong rapport and alleviating concerns
- Reduced the overall project time by developing a training matrix to track staff competencies and documentation from previous training courses

#### Sales Administrator, Breville, Sydney (Australia Working Holiday Visa)

JUNE 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Analysed price changes of company products and those of competing firms across different online stores whilst highlighting sizeable variances between them
- Created Amazon store web listings for the entire product range of the companies products

#### Supply Chain Coordinator, Sherwin Williams

FEBRUARY 2017 - OCTOBER 2018

- Head Oracle production user, directly responsible for 3 out of 7 production KPIs and managing the ERP system
- Improved the reporting of finished stock quantities by implementing improvements for the Oracle ERP production workflow, increasing the reported quantity by over a thousand pallets a year
- Identified issues with paint volume discrepancies resulting in waste quantities being over-reported by hundreds of thousands of litres
- Decreased supply-chain costs by executing a revamped system for managing the rework process that applied root cause analysis to identify faults
- Created a suite of SOPs for supply chain systems to facilitate the continued training of staff based on auditors' requirements.
- Trained operators on the correct usage of Oracle OPM interfaces for completing works orders
- Amended on-hand stock discrepancies & oversaw operations for the finished goods dispatch area

#### Store Colleague, ASDA

SEPTEMBER 2012 - DECEMBER 2016

Worked to ensure a positive and hassle-free customer experience by adopting
a warm and friendly service culture, additionally undertook extra shifts based
on the needs of the company

#### Additional Work

- Previously volunteered as a Charity Shop Assistant, Teaching Assistant, Accounts Assistant and Hostel Receptionist
- Completed several months of physically intensive regional work to obtain a second Australian Working Holiday Visa
- Student Ambassador at the University of Leeds.